Alrighty todays daily challenge
The Financier Stealth
Hidden UI
Unintimidating
and No Lockpicks
So we've got a drill again
with precision drilling
but once again we got unintimidating
and hidden UI.
Hidden UI is not that bad
unintimidating is really the worst
part
because that means
we are gonna actually have to
hack the computer for this
Yup
And also I am pretty sure I've lured
that camera so we're just gonna bag this body
and get right out of there
because I was not careful
going up here
and we won't even know because its hidden UI.
That is not a good way of doing it
Lets just run down there
since no one is going to show up
over there
probably
You know what yeah we should
probably just back off
grab the disguise over here and
not worry about it
Cyber did you also just
Right then that's another guard taken
care of I suppose
which I mean sure
Now all we got to do i—
This is too good,
this is literally too good
You turn yourself in that direction
Alright
Never mind
We'll just loop the camera regardless
I mean otherwise we
would have just taken out that guard
we'll rewire this power box and then
afterwards
we'll deal with the remaining
power boxes
and
probably also the guard at this rate
So that's exactly what we're
going to do
we will completely ignore this guard because
that is absolutely not helpful to us
and you know what we'll seize the
opportunity and knock that guard out in
the perfect location
Cyber's got the last power box
actually which means that what I'm gonna do
is I'm going to go up here run
past that camera for absolutely no
reason
or actually a very good reason which is
to—
not getting caught by those two
I mean that's literally the worst
combination to be caught by but regardless
we get this door completely open
Cyber should probably loop that camera at some point
because it's going to help us out
a lot
and actually because I'm about to
open this door
So
You know what
We'll loop it it's fine
we'll go backwards we'll go past this
and we loop that camera
and it's gonna go just fine
we've got a guard there
but we don't have to worry about it
the guard is not going to care
I mean the guard would see the open
doorway
except for one small caveat
the door is blocking the guard from
seeing the open doorway
and therefore
detecting the broken door
which is certainly not a way
I mean it's
it's certainly a good way of not getting
caught
and I'm not going to complain about it
so we'll go past all of that and we will—
right then we'll go back through here
and we will hope
we will hope that there are no guards
over here to mess with us
we'll start with this photograph of
course
and it seems to be going well
and now all we got to do is not get caught by
Ryan or any of the remaining guards over there
which
is harder than it seems because
that's exactly what's happening right now.
So instead
Why Ryan
no you're not doing that all right
Just to make it clear
Never mind you are doing that
There's not much I can do about it so
we'll go back over here and we will
this is actually perfect I
mean— All right
We're going to go past all of this, it's
going to be okay
and we're going to get
the safe location
and we'll take advantage of it to open up the safe
so once the photographs remove we'll
open up the safe
grab the hard drive
and now all we got to do is find Ryan
which won't be—
Really?
Which wont be difficult at all
absolutely worth it I mean that guard
almost
got lured
but we should be fine
Now really all we got to do right now is do this
The safe door is being a major
nuisance over here
but I think I I'm still
able to do it so Ryan look at me over here
Do me a favor and walk over here
and just in time
Right then we are grabbing this bag
and we are getting right out of here
I mean it's probably a good idea
regardless
So that's exactly what we're
going to do we're going to leave this area
and Cyber the doors open over here
you might just want to leave through that
And that's the daily challenge in
just under 5 minutes
I mean that ending wasn't
exactly too plan
but it worked so I'm
not going to complain about that
Cheers everyone,
have a great time.
[Music]